myprivatesearch.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy - MyPrivateSearch

## Privacy Policy

“My Private Search” engine and browser extension (hereinafter " **Service** " or “ **Extension** ” or “ **MPS** ”) provides a private search without tracking. These and “My Private Search” EULA/Terms of Service (" **Terms** ") are the accesses and terms of your use of the extension.

**Information We Collect**

It is important to emphasize that MPS does not collect or share its user’s personal information.

Despite the fact that other search engines may receive information when users provide, we chose not to collect and/or use this information. For instance, if you search a product, other search engines may collect your email address, country of origin, and, if you choose, your nickname, telephone number, website, search history and title, but different from other search sites, we respect all our user’s privacy.

We also gave up collecting your web searches, including but not limited, your IP address, click ID and this information is not saved on our servers and not logged in a way that we could identify you or be traced back to you.

The only information we collect is a non-personal information in order to manage and improve our business and services. This information includes for example how did you hear about us, how did you download the extension, when did you download it etc. It is the time to mention one more time that this information cannot be used in order to identify you.

**Cookies**

At MPS, we don’t advocate in using cookies. In case our user changes settings, then our cookies are used to store those changes. But still, we do not store them or know how to trace you by them. As mentioned, we may use cookies in order to know how did you find us but with no relation to your search actions.

We also sampling part of the searches, but again, not in a personally identifiable way, as we do not store IP addresses or unique User ID.

**Uninstall**

If you decided to uninstall My Private Search browser extension, you just need to follow the instructions on this link:

Uninstall Link

**Security**

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our extension, you can contact us.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this extension prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at Contact Us
